<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home_page on Reviving Anabaptism in the Netherlands</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/</link><description>Recent content in Home_page on Reviving Anabaptism in the Netherlands</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://anabaptist.nl/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>shropshire_bibleconf_2025</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/shropshire-mennonite-bible-conference-2025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/shropshire-mennonite-bible-conference-2025/</guid><description>Invitation We have received, and give you the following invitation to the 2025 Shropshire Bible Conference, hosted by UK Mennonite Ministries, also called the Shropshire Hills Mennonite church, located in Craven Arms, Shropshire, England. A printable version is here
You are invited to our 18th annual Bible Conference 5 - 7 December 2025, Lord Willing
Cefn Lea Park, Dolfor, Newtown,
Powys, Wales, SY16 4AJ
Hosted by Shropshire Hills Mennonite Church</description></item><item><title>love_from_poland</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/love-from-poland/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/love-from-poland/</guid><description>To all who seek God&amp;rsquo;s will in your life; you are greeted with love from our brother and sister in Poland. We were blessed to be able to meet recently, after several almost-meetings in the past years that we have had contact. It was a blessed time together, and a memory we will cherish.
On Monday, we went to the zoo in Krakow. It was a joyous experience to see the wonder in children&amp;rsquo;s eyes at the marvels of God&amp;rsquo;s creation.</description></item><item><title>twee_koninkrijken</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/twee-koninkrijken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/twee-koninkrijken/</guid><description>The teaching of the two kingdoms is, for many christians, an unknown and sometimes uncomfortable subject. It is hardly taught or spoken of, and yet it was Jesus himself who brought us the message, right from the beginning of His preaching: "Now after that John was put in prison, Jesus came into Galilee, preaching the gospel of the kingdom of God" Mark 1:14 .
Imagine: Jack is the ambassador to Japan.</description></item><item><title>the_lord_provideth</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/the-lord-provideth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/the-lord-provideth/</guid><description>PROVERBS 16:3 Commit thy works unto the LORD, and thy thoughts shall be established.
I was at a convention of Christians, and there was much singing. A man from Ukraine said to me; &amp;rsquo;the Lord provideth! He sent so much food, what was I to do? Of course, I filled the granary. He sent grain, even oxen, everything we needed.&amp;rsquo; A woman from England said; &amp;lsquo;you couldn&amp;rsquo;t even do that here.</description></item><item><title>db_in_nl</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/dunkard-brethren-in-nl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/dunkard-brethren-in-nl/</guid><description>We are Dunkard Brethren Hello! My wife and I are overjoyed to announce that we were baptised in the name of our Lord and Saviour, Jesus Christ. In doing so we became full members of the Dunkard Brethren church, and it is our hope that more will join us in Europe. A wonderful peace accompanies us in knowing we have elders we can trust, and brothers and sisters we can rely on for support.</description></item><item><title>beachy_amish_in_ireland</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/beachy-amish-in-ireland/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/beachy-amish-in-ireland/</guid><description>The Amish Mennonite Church of Waterford was established in 1992, supported by the Beachy Amish Mennonite Fellowship Churches in the United States through the Mennonite Interests Committee (MIC), which provides financial and material support and organises their mission work in Europe.
Why Ireland? There were two local couples in search of anabaptist Christian fellowship to stablish and strengthen their convictions. After sending two of their ministers to investigate the conditions of various regions in Ireland, they established the Portally Cove mission near Dunmore East (in Waterford county), which is now called the Dunmore East Christian Fellowship.</description></item><item><title>importance_of_being_honest</title><link>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/absolute-truthfullness/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://anabaptist.nl/en/articles/absolute-truthfullness/</guid><description>The Lord&amp;rsquo;s command Have you ever heard of a white lie? When you tell someone something just to sound pleasing or comforting to them, you take a step away from the Lord, who loves only the truth. When He gave us the ten commandments, He told us in no uncertain terms that we should never lie. Just as the commandment forbidding murder made no exceptions for the king&amp;rsquo;s executioner or the soldier on the battlefield, the Lord said:</description></item></channel></rss>